https://www.websitepulse.com/corporate/privacy.policy.php#cookie

We are using cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website. To find out more, please read our Privacy Policy section.   Got it!
WebSitePulse Privacy Policy
This policy explains how WebSitePulse collects, shares, stores and uses data. Typically, we collect customer data in order to provide the services that customers purchase or request from us. For example, we may capture email addresses so that a customer can check the status of their monitoring services or open a case with our tech support team. We collect visitor data through our website (www.websitepulse.com and its related subdomains) in order to understand and improve our website content, as well as maintain a secure computing environment. When we collect this data, we do so in compliance with this privacy policy, which describes how we handle the data we collect in more detail. This policy also describes other important topics relating to information privacy.
1. Data Collection and Usage
We may collect and process any of the following information about you and we refer to this as “Personal Information” throughout this policy:
1.1 Account information
You may give us information about yourself by using the online forms provided on the Website or by contacting us by phone, e-mail or other means.
The information you give us may include: email address, name, mailing address, telephone number, messaging handles, company name, company address, credit card information, job title, account information, and any updates to information provided to us.
Please note that we need certain types of information so that we can provide services to you. If you do not provide us with such information, or if you ask us to delete it, you may no longer be able to access our services.
This information may be used for the following purposes:
to allow you to access and use the Website and to register for an account;
to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us via the website, email, phone call or other channels such as “Live Chat”
to allow you to participate in interactive features, such as “Live Chat”, when you choose to do so.
to notify you about changes to our products or services and to keep you informed about our fees and charges.
to carry out activities in the legitimate interests of WebSitePulse, for example, pursuing debt, ensuring the security of our services and Website;
to verify your identity in order to prevent and detect money laundering and fraud;
to take other action you request when you supply the Information.
1.2 Contact information
This is the information you give us so we could send you monitoring alerts and reports – it may include name, email addresses, telephone number, messaging contacts.
Additionally when you use our mobile apps and request us to send you alerts via those apps we will collect the device ID. This information will be used to provide the service(s) you have requested like sending monitoring alerts and reports to the contacts you have configured carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
1.3 System log
Every change to your account settings will be logged with date/time, IP address, user identifier and URL. This information is available to the users authorized by you or the account administrator and may be reviewed by our staff when tracking a security issue or upon request from an authorized account user.
1.4 Information we collect about you.
Each time you visit the Website we may automatically collect some technical information
including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect to our site, the URL you have requested, date/time of the request, domain name and country which requests information, browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform.
Such data is anonymised as far as is reasonably possible and you will not be identifiable from the data collected. It will be used for the purposes of improving and maintaining our Website, preparing reports or compiling statistics in order to improve our services.
3. Data Retention.
We retain Personal Information for as long as you use the services we provide and then as required to comply with applicable laws.
4. Disclosure of Information.
We will not sell, hire, lease, rent or in any way share your Personal Information that we collect to any third party except as expressly set forth in this Section.
4.1 Categories of Third Parties:
Any third parties with whom we share your Personal Information are limited (by law and by contract) in their ability to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than to provide services for us. We will always ensure that any third parties with whom we share your Personal Information are subject to privacy and security obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. We will share your Personal Information with the following categories of third parties:
our service providers including but not limited to payment processors and suppliers of live-chat services;
analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our Website;
4.2 Other Third-Party Disclosures.
We will also disclose your Personal Information to third parties:
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Information in order to comply with any legal obligation, any lawful request from government or law enforcement officials and as may be required to meet national security or law enforcement requirements or prevent illegal activity;
in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions or any other agreement or to respond to any claims, to protect our rights or the rights of a third party, to protect the safety of any person or to prevent any illegal activity;
to protect the rights, property, or safety of WebSitePulse, our customers or other persons. This may include exchanging information with other organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
5. Data transfer
WebSitePulse is an USA based company and accordingly this website and most of its related assets are located in the United States. If you are located outside the United States and provide Personal Information to us, we will transfer your Personal Information to the United States and use it there in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
The Personal Information may also be processed by staff operating in the United States or outside the EEA or Switzerland working for us. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of our services to you, the processing of transactions and/or the provision of support services. By providing us with your Personal Information you acknowledge any such transfer, storage and processing.
We will always take steps to ensure that such transfers comply with applicable privacy laws and we will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that your Personal Information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
6. Protection of Personal Information
WebSitePulse is committed to taking steps to protect the Information you provide to us, including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to safeguard Information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.
Information is accessed only by authorized staff who are instructed to handle Information with confidentiality. It is protected by firewalls and standard industry security measures. We will also transmit sensitive information and transactional data using strong encryption.
Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Website or our services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
7. Your Rights
You may contact us at any time, to request that we:
update any Personal Information which is out of date or incorrect;
delete any Personal Information which we are holding about you;
restrict the way that we process your Personal Information;
provide you with a copy of any Personal Information which we hold about you.
We will consider all such requests and provide our response within a reasonable time period. We commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information (without charge to you).
8. Use of Cookies
Some pages on our Website use cookies, which are small files placed on your internet browser when you visit our Website. We uses cookies for your convenience to store your session and preferences information so you do not have to reenter your data upon each visit.
When you visit our websites, cookies will be placed on your computer or device to maximize your experience and to help us understand how we can improve our site.  If you prefer not to receive cookies, you can set your browser to either reject all cookies, to allow “trusted” sites to set them, or to accept only those cookies from those sites you are currently on.  However, turning off cookies will hinder your ability to access, use, or navigate portions of the site.
9. Third Party Websites
The Website may, from time to time, contain links to websites operated by third parties. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected from the Website and we cannot be responsible for Personal Information collected and stored by third-parties. If you choose to visit any of those sites, then their privacy policies would apply and you should read these carefully before you submit any Personal Information to these websites. We do not endorse or otherwise accept any responsibility or liability for the content of such third-party websites or third party terms and conditions or policies.
10. Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. By continuing to use the services and our Website, you agree to the latest version of our Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy
11. Contact Us
If you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy or how we collect, use or store your Personal Information, you can contact us by phone at: +1-407-380-1600
or by email at support@websitepulse.com
Services
Server Monitoring
Webpage Monitoring
Web Transaction Monitoring
Email Round-trip Monitoring
Vulnerability Monitoring
Blacklist Monitoring
Copyright 2000-2020, WebSitePulse. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
